In a dark corner, an endless lesson, and a mind drifting far away.
في زاويةٍ مظلمة، درسٌ لا ينتهي، وعقلٌ شاردٌ بعيد.
But a mother saw what no one else did... she searched for another way, and found PlayVerse.
لكنَّ أمّاً رأت ما لم يرَهُ أحد... فبحثت عن طريقٍ آخر، ووجدت PlayVerse.
One touch... and the light burst forth.
لمسةٌ واحدة... وانفجرَ النور.
The lesson became an adventure, and the screen an enchanted island.
تحوَّل الدرسُ إلى مغامرة، والشاشةُ إلى جزيرةٍ مسحورة.
A glowing river, and a secret waiting.
نهرٌ يتوهج، وسِرٌّ ينتظر.
A drop of water given with a kind heart... opens the doors to treasure.
قطرةُ ماءٍ بطيبةِ قلب... تفتحُ أبوابَ الكنوز.
Biology is a living forest, physics a glowing universe, and math a world to discover.
الأحياءُ غابةٌ حيّة، والفيزياءُ كونٌ متوهّج، والرياضياتُ عالمٌ يُكتشف.
And with the right answer... the hero wins.
وبالجوابِ الصحيح... ينتصرُ البطل.
Then he returns... thirsty for knowledge, not running from it.
ثمَّ يعود... متعطشاً للمعرفة، لا هارباً منها.
PlayVerse: learn, play, compete — on every platform.
PlayVerse: تعلّم، إلعب، تنافس على كل المنصات.
And through the PlayVerse app, you enter worlds without limits.
ومن خلال تطبيق PlayVerse، تدخل عوالم لا حدود لها.
A gateway to every passion and every kind of knowledge.
بوابةٌ لكل شغفٍ ومعرفة.
One touch... and curiosity catches fire.
لمسةٌ واحدة... فيشتعلُ الفضول.
Literature is told like a story, and science dances in your hands.
الأدبُ يُروى كأنه حكاية، والعلومُ تتراقصُ بين يديك.
From your seat... straight into the heart of the adventure.
من مقعدك... إلى قلب المغامرة.
You learn together, no matter how far apart you are.
تتعلمون معاً مهما بَعُدَت الديار.
And every correct answer... is a new victory.
وكل إجابة صحيحة... نصرٌ جديد.
PlayVerse: your world to learn, play and compete.
PlayVerse: عالمك للتعلم واللعب والتنافس.
The exam is hard.
الامتحان صعب.
With us... you are not just a student, you are a warrior.
أنت معنا... لستَ مجرد طالب، أنت محارب.
The exam is not hard.
ليس الامتحان صعباً.
This is no barrier to my will!
ليس هذا حاجزاً أمام إرادتي!